{
    "subject": "resource/Makhdoom_Bilawal",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Saint",
    "human_readable": "Makhdoom Bilawal is considered a Saint.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881207942962646,
            "question": "Is Makhdoom Bilawal considered a Saint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9659733176231384,
            "question": "Who revered Makhdoom Bilawal as a Saint?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7422472238540649,
            "question": "What is Makhdoom Bilawal known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6117679476737976,
            "question": "What religious figure is Makhdoom Bilawal associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6037223935127258,
            "question": "Where is Makhdoom Bilawal venerated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5620511770248413,
            "question": "What is the significance of Makhdoom Bilawal in religious history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4095595180988312,
            "question": "Are there any places of worship dedicated to Makhdoom Bilawal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38572463393211365,
            "question": "Are there any stories or legends about Makhdoom Bilawal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37711432576179504,
            "question": "What time period was Makhdoom Bilawal active in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2926992177963257,
            "question": "What impact did Makhdoom Bilawal have on people's lives?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Makhdoom Bilawal is considered a Saint.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period was Makhdoom Bilawal active in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any stories or legends about Makhdoom Bilawal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any places of worship dedicated to Makhdoom Bilawal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2806_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several instances where Makhdoom Bilawal is referred to as a saint, including phrases such as \"Makhdoom Bilawal is revered as a saint\", \"His shrine is located at Baghban near Dadu, where thousands of people visit every year to pay their respects and seek his blessings.\", and \"He was popularly knows as Makhdoom Bilawal (R.A)\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Makhdoom Bilawal is revered as a saint, with phrases such as \"Makhdoom Bilawal is revered as a saint, a hero and a national symbol by the Sindhis\" and \"He Belonged to Samma Royalty and was a member of the ruling family of Thatta,\" indicating his high status in Sindh's culture."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}